{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_Kloeppel",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Frankfurt",
    "human_readable": "Peter Kloeppel was born in Frankfurt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8903625011444092,
            "question": "Where was Peter Kloeppel born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8176257610321045,
            "question": "In what year was Peter Kloeppel born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6847844123840332,
            "question": "What is Peter Kloeppel's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5715899467468262,
            "question": "What is Peter Kloeppel known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.500347375869751,
            "question": "Where did Peter Kloeppel live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44810184836387634,
            "question": "What city is associated with Peter Kloeppel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4375310242176056,
            "question": "What is Peter Kloeppel's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.393083393573761,
            "question": "Does Peter Kloeppel have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3880806565284729,
            "question": "Is Peter Kloeppel a public figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3078296184539795,
            "question": "Where did Peter Kloeppel go to school?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter Kloeppel was born in Frankfurt.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8460_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Peter Kloeppel a public figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8460_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Peter Kloeppel have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8460_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Peter Kloeppel's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8460_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8460_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n\n\nThe documents don't mention where Peter Kloeppel was born, only that he completed his Abitur in Bad Homburg in 1977. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"no\" }`\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents do not contain any information about Peter Kloeppel's place of birth. The only mention of his birth year is \"1970\", but there is no location specified.\n\nIn particular, document 1.txt mentions that Kloeppel attended school in Bad Homburg and studied agriculture in G\u00f6ttingen, but it does not provide any information about where he was born. Therefore, the statement \"Peter Kloeppel was born in Frankfurt\" cannot be confirmed based on the provided documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information to support the claim that Peter Kloeppel was born in Frankfurt. The available information states his date of birth as 1970, but there is no mention of the place of birth."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that indicates Peter Kloeppel was born in Frankfurt.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple pieces of context state his birth year and education/career path, none mentioning Frankfurt as a birthplace.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there is no information provided to support the birthplace of Peter Kloeppel being Frankfurt, while his other details are mentioned in different context which indicates that Peter Kloeppel was born on 1970 but not in Frankfurt and another context mentions Peter Kloeppel was born in 1958.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provides Peter Kloeppel's birth year as 1970 but does not specify his birthplace. There is no mention of Frankfurt or any other specific city, so we cannot confirm the claim based on the given information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}